Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Correspondence, ca. 1967-1998, Series 2; Boxes 112-144
  - Literary correspondence, ca. 1967-1997, Subseries 2.2; Boxes 124-128
    - McGough, Roger, 1972-1983 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, 1991-1992 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - McGuinness, Frank, 1986 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - McNulty, Ted, 1991-1992 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - McPhee, John, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - McSweeney, Barry, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - MacCaig, Norman, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1977-1980 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - MacMahon, Bryan, 1984-1985 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - MacManus, Patricia, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - MacSiomon, Tom, 1981-1982 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Madden, Deirdre, 1983, 1991 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Magee, Wes, 1969-1989 (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - Marcus, Dennis, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Martin, James, 1977 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Meek, Jay, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Meenan, Hugo, 1982-1983 (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - Mercier, Vivian, 1980-1984 (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Miller, Liam, 1983 (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - Milne, Ewart, 1975-1982 (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - Mitchell, Adrian, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - Molloy, M.J., 1978-1993 (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - Mooney, Martin, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 37)
    - Moore, Brian, 1979-1983 (Box 126, Folder 38)
    - Moore, Christy, 1987-1995 (Box 126, Folder 39)
    - Morgan, Pete, 1969-1979 (Box 126, Folder 40)
    - Morrison, Blake, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 41)
    - Morrow, John, 1968-1970 (Box 126, Folder 42)
    - Moss, Howard, 1982, with three Peter Fallon poems (Box 126, Folder 43)
    - Motion, Andrew, 1983-1984 (Box 126, Folder 44)
    - Muldoon, Paul, 1992-1995, with letter from Peter Fallon (Box 126, Folder 45)
    - Murphy, Aidan, 1978-1982 (Box 126, Folder 46)
    - Murphy, Michael, J., 1982 (Box 126, Folder 47)
    - Murphy, Mike, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 48)
    - Murphy, Richard, 1978-1986, with TS poems (Box 126, Folder 49)
    - Murphy, Thomas, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 50)
    - Nims, John Frederick, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, George, 1986-1991 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor, 1993-1995 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - O'Callaghan, Julie, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - O'Connor, Ulick, 1981, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - O Cuilleanáin, Eilís, 1973-1980 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Ó Díreáin, Máirtín, 1979-1990 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - O'Donnell, Mary, 1985-1988 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - O'Donnell, Peadar, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - O'Donoghue, Robert, early 1970s (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - O'Driscoll, Dennis, 1977-1995 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Ó Faoláin, Eilean, 1979-1985 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - O'Flynn, Criostoir, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, 1978-1990 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Ó Siadhail, Mícheál, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - O'Sullivan, D.J., 1982 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - O'Toole, Fintan, 1984-1985 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Offner, Elliot, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Ormsby, Frank, 1996 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Patten, Brian, 1974-1980s (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - Paulin, Tom, 1979-1988 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Pearson, Henry, 1980-1994 (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Peel, John, 1970-1977, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - Peskett, William, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Plunkett, James, 1977-1979 (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - Quinn, Justin, 1994, 1998 (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Quinn, Ruairi, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - Reardon, Daniel, 1974-1996 (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Riordan, Maurice, 1985, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 31)
    - Ronsley, Joe, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 32)
    - Scammell, Bill, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 33)
    - Schaeffer, Susan, 1972-1975 (Box 127, Folder 34)
    - Seay, James, 1974-1978 (Box 127, Folder 35)
    - Shaw, Elizabeth, 1985-1986 (Box 127, Folder 36)
    - Simmons, James, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 37)
    - Simpson, Louis, 1978-1979 (Box 127, Folder 38)
    - Skinner, Knute, 1969-1986 (Box 127, Folder 39)
    - Smith, John, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 40)
    - Smith, Michael, 1973-1988 (Box 127, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Sydney Bernard, 1978, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 42)
    - Smyth, Gerard, 1975-1984 (Box 127, Folder 43)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1983-1984 (Box 127, Folder 44)
    - Sommer, Pioter, 1980-1993 (Box 127, Folder 45)
    - Spear, Roberta, 1984 (Box 127, Folder 46)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1994 (Box 127, Folder 47)
    - Stafford, William, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 48)
    - Strong, Eithne, 1971-1979 (Box 127, Folder 49)
    - Stuart, Francis, 1974-1986 (Box 127, Folder 50)
    - Sweeney, Jack, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 51)
    - Sweeney, Matthew, 1973-1977 (Box 127, Folder 52)
    - Tailer, Kitty, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 53)
    - Tall, Deborah, 1976-1983 (Box 127, Folder 54)
    - Tamburro, Florence, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 55)
    - Thompson, Sam, 1991 (Box 127, Folder 56)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, 1991-1992 (Box 127, Folder 57)
    - Taibin, Colin, 1971-1972 (Box 127, Folder 58)
    - Trevor, William, ca. 1979 (Box 127, Folder 59)
    - Trow, Greg, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 60)
    - Valentine, Jean, 1989-1993 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Vendler, Helen, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Voigt, Ellen Bryant, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Wake, Brian, 1969-1973 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - West, Anthony C., 1981-1984 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Wilbur, Richard, 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Hugo, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Woods, Gordon, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Wyley, Edna, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Yaguchi, Yoritumi, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Yeats, Anne, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Young, Augustus, 1975-1976 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - RESTRICTED CORRESPONDENCE
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1970-1983 (Box 128a, Folder 1)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 128a, Folder 2)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 128a, Folder 3)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 128a, Folder 4)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 128a, Folder 5)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 128a, Folder 6)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 128a, Folder 7)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 128a, Folder 8)
    - Heaney, Seamus - Correspondence, n.d (Box 128a, Folder 9)
  - Business correspondence, ca. 1970-1998, Subseries 2.3; Boxes 129-144
    - Patrick Kavanagh royalties
    - Royalties, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Royalties, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Royalties, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Royalties, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Royalties, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Royalties, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Royalties, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Royalties, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Royalties, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Royalties, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Royalties, 1995 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Royalties, 1996 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Royalties, 1997 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Patrick Kavanagh permissions
    - Permissions, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Permissions, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Permissions, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Permissions, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Permissions, 1991-1993 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Permissions, 1993-1994 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Permissions, 1994 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, 1995 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Permissions, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Permissions, 1997 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Patrick Kavanagh subject files
    - Bank Accounts (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - BBC (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - BBC (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - BBC (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Cladding (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - "The Early Years of Patrick Kavanagh" (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Egan, Desmond (Goldsmith Press) (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - "Eileán" (Eileán Ní Chuilleanain) (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - IMRO (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Inniskeen (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Jay, John (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - "Kavanagh" (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Kavanagh, Katherine (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Katherine and Peter Kavanagh Rights Dispute (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Maloney, Paddy (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - MCPS (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - MCPS (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - MCPS (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - MCPS (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - MCPS (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - MCPS (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - MCPS (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - MCPS (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - MCPS, England (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - MCPS, Ireland (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - "Mucker" (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - O'Keefe, Timothy (Martin Brian and O'Keefe, Ltd) (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Penguin (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Penguin Books Ltd (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - RTE (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - "Raglan Road" Dispute (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Received and accounted for (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Selected poems (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Tax exemption (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - To do (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - To do (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1971-1997
    - Permissions and royalties, 1971-1983 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1984-1985 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Permissions and royalties, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Permissions, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Royalties, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Permissions, Blackstafff Press, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Permissions, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Permissions, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Permissions, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Permissions, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Permissions, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Permissions, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Permissions, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Permissions, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Permissions, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Permissions and Royalties, 1997 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, 1997 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Contracts
    - Archer, Nuala (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Banville, John (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Behan, Beatrice (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Cannon, Moya (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Carr, Marina (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Carson, Ciaran (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Clifton, Harry (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Coady, Michael (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Dawe, Gerald (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Deane, Seamus (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Durcan, Paul (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Durkan, Michael (Walsh, Maeve) (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Glavin, Anthony (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Grennan, Eamon (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Groake, Vona (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Hardie, Kerry (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Harnett, Michael (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Harvey, Francis (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Healy, Dermot (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Hughes, John (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Hutchinson, Pearse (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Kilroy, Thomas (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Lysaght, Seán (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - MacIntyre, Tom (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Magee, Heno (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Mahon, Derek (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Mathews, Aidan (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - McCabe, Eugene (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - McGuckian, Medbh (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - McGuiness, Frank (Box 139, Folder 31)
    - Meehan, Paula (Box 139, Folder 32)
    - Montague, John (Box 139, Folder 33)
    - Muldoon, Paul (Box 139, Folder 34)
    - Ní Chuilleanáin, Eiléan (Box 139, Folder 35)
    - Ni Dhomhnaill, Nuala (Box 139, Folder 36)
    - Nolan, Jim (Box 139, Folder 37)
    - O'Callaghan, Conor (Box 139, Folder 38)
    - O'Donoghue, Bernard (Box 139, Folder 39)
    - O'Grady, Desmond (Box 139, Folder 40)
    - Ó Muirthile, Liam (Box 139, Folder 41)
    - Ormsby, Frank (Box 139, Folder 42)
    - Parker, Stewart (Box 139, Folder 43)
    - Rodgers, W.R. (Box 139, Folder 44)
    - Simmons, James (Box 139, Folder 45)
    - Sirr, Peter (Box 139, Folder 46)
    - Wheatley, David (Box 139, Folder 47)
    - Subject Files
    - Bell and Bain Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Catalogue Requests and Book Orders (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Co-Publishing Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Office Help: Ad and Replies (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Proscenium Press Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Publisher Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Billings and Son (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Booksellers A-J (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Booksellers L-Z (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Booksellers-Bay Side Books (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Booksellers-Bertram Rota, Ltd. (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Booksellers-Facsimile Book Shop (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Booksellers-Grolier Book Shop (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Booksellers-Peter Joliffe (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Booksellers-Kenny's Bookshop (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Booksellers-Naughton Booksellers (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Booksellers-Oriel Bookshop (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Booksellers-Charles Seluzicki Poetry Bookseller (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Business Correspondence, 1973-1998 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Irish Elsevier Printers Limited (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Librarians (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Printers and Binders (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Printers, Binders, and Photographers (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - SciPrint (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Wake Forest University (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Financial records
    - Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Orders, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Orders (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1975-1979 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1975-1979 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1975-1979 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1975-1979 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1975-1979 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, 1980-1983 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Receipts (US Trip), 1981 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, Orders, Invoices, Etc., 1983-1994 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Addresses, Phone Numbers, Business Cards (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Peter Fallon personal papers, ca. 1968-1998, Series 3; Boxes 145-166
  The series consists of the literary and personal papers of Peter Fallon from ca. 1968-1998. The papers include writings by Peter Fallon including manuscripts and typescripts of his poetry, prose, music and plays; works edited by Fallon; materials relating to his appearances including lectures, speeches, interviews, and readings by Fallon; the printed material consists mostly of reviews of Fallon's work and copies of periodicals in which his works appeared.
  Organized into four subseries: (3.1) Writings by Peter Fallon, (3.2) Works edited by Peter Fallon, (3.3) Appearances by Peter Fallon, (3.4) Printed material, and (3.5) Appointment books and calendars.
  - Writings by Peter Fallon, ca. 1968-1998, Subseries 3.1; Boxes 145-154
    - Manuscript Notebooks
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1974 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1975 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript Notebook, ca. 1975 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript notebook, ca. 1976 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Unbound MS notes and notebooks (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Poems
    - "All We Could Do," TS (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - "Always I Have Walked in Darkness," ca. Feb. 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - "Among the Harshest Hours," ca. November 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - "And all the While the Rain Was Falling," ca. March 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - "And One There Was Whose Leaves Were Blown," October 1971, TS (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - "The Appointment" ("Loughcrew: Early Spring 1971") [See: "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "At the Other Side of Dawn," ca. 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - "August" ("August, 1980"), ca. 1980, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - "The Autumn Hunter," ca. November 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - "Autumn Park Poem," ca. December 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - "Bass harmonies beyond the window...," TS (fragment) (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - "The Beast," ca. 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - "Bethzatha," ca. April 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - "Blackwater," pre-1995, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - "Bohemian Girl," Summer 1967 and May 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - "The Book We Lived By," TS (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - "Care," ca. 1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - "Carnaross," (1), pre-1987, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - "Carolina," ca. 1987, TS (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - "Cordelia," December 1968 and December 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - "Dandelion," ca. 1973, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - "Diary Note," 1973, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - "Dublin," MS (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - "Dunlavin," TS (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - "Emerson at Fresh Fields" [See "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "Epitaph," ca. November 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - "Epithalamium," [1] MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - "Epithalamium," (2) (for Charlie and Emily), 26 September 1981, TS (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - "Especially After Evening Rain," early works, TS (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - "Fable," ca. August 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - "The First Born," 1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - "For You My Love (after the French of Prevert)," February 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - "Forms," TS (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - "Fowl: four poems," (Matins, Ducks, Hens, Turkeys), pre-1995, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - "The Further Furrows," TS (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - "Harvest Home," TS (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - "He is grieving at the bar...," TS (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - "He rode eight miles to say...," TS (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - "He Tells His Love," ca. 1975, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 37)
    - "The Healer," TS and MS (Box 146, Folder 38)
    - "Helios," ca. December 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 39)
    - "Her Coloured Cardigan," 1974-1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 40)
    - "I Am Achilles," MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 41)
    - "I Gave Love," 1967, TS (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - "I will not mourn...," TS (Box 146, Folder 43)
    - "Il va neiger" (from "De l'Angelus de l'Aube; l'Angelus du Soir"), ca. 1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 44)
    - "Il y a par la," MS (Box 146, Folder 45)
    - "Interlude," MS (Box 146, Folder 46)
    - "An Interlude," ca. 1986, TS (Box 146, Folder 47)
    - "It was not the day...," TS (Box 146, Folder 48)
    - "January Song," 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 49)
    - "The Jones Place" [See "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "Late Blood," 1972-1975, TS [c.f. "Piecings" in The First Affair] (Box 146, Folder 50)
    - "Letter from the Country," ca. 1973-75, MS [c.f. "Person to Person"] (Box 146, Folder 51)
    - "Listen, the Night Has Grown So Still," June 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 52)
    - "Little Christmas," pre-1989, TS (Box 146, Folder 53)
    - "Love Letters," ca. 1987, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 54)
    - "Lunasa," pre-1995, TS (Box 146, Folder 55)
    - "Maggie," ca. 1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 56)
    - "The Map of Time," TS (Box 146, Folder 57)
    - "Maverick" (Originally "Gravities" no. 11), ca. 1982, TS (Box 146, Folder 58)
    - "Midlands," ca. 1975, TS (Box 146, Folder 59)
    - "The Morning Less Romantic," ca. 1973, TS [contains fragment of "Moth" on back] (Box 146, Folder 60)
    - "Moth" ("Primordial"), ca. 1974, TS [with fragment of "Island"] (Box 146, Folder 61)
    - "Mount," TS (Box 146, Folder 62)
    - "My Love Has Gone or Never Come," ca. May 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 63)
    - "My neighbour's fathers owned the land...," MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 64)
    - "The News," TS wiith corrections (Box 146, Folder 65)
    - "Not That We Have Chosen Silence," September 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 66)
    - "Nought," ca. 1973, TS [fragment of "Reprieve" on back] (Box 146, Folder 67)
    - "Olden," 1976, TS (Box 146, Folder 68)
    - "Orm," 1976, TS [See also MS Notebook, ca. 1973-1974] (Box 146, Folder 69)
    - "Parkscene," ca. May 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 70)
    - "Party," ca. August 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 71)
    - "The Party Being Over," April 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 72)
    - "The Pearl," ca. 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 73)
    - "Penates," ca. 1975-76, MS (Box 146, Folder 74)
    - "The Perseids" [See: "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "Person to Person," ca. 1974, MS [c.f. "Letter from the Country"; contains early fragment of "Reprieve" and other poems] (Box 146, Folder 75)
    - "A Poem" ("And I Have Watched Two Old Men..."), ca. April 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 76)
    - "Prey," MS (Box 146, Folder 77)
    - "The Price," MS (Box 146, Folder 78)
    - "Primary Colours" [See: "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "Reprieve" ("The Morning Your Mother Brought us Breakfast"), ca. 1974, MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 79)
    - "Riddle," MS and TS (Box 146, Folder 80)
    - "The River," TS and artwork for Limited Edition Broadside (1993) (Box 146, Folder 81)
    - "A Rose for Emily" (Translation of "Eine Rose für Emilia" by Peter Fallon), ca. May 1969, TS (Box 146, Folder 82)
    - "Sad that one 'phone call...," ca. July 1970, TS (Box 146, Folder 83)
    - "A Seaside Hotel," October 1987, TS (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - "Seen Once Again Wand'ring By River," ca. 1972, TS (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - "'She mentions harvests...,'" TS (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - "She's Beautiful," TS (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - "Sliabh na Cailli: Straws" [parts became "Home" from Winter Work] (Box OP62)
    - "Small Ancient Wars," MS and TS (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - "Snow," MS (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - "Soldier" ("Like a Light in the dark"), mid 1970s, TS (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - "Some," TS (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - "Storm-child," 8 September 1985, MS and TS (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - "Star," ca. June 1969, TS (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - "A Strong Weakness" ("Grandfather"), ca. 1975, MS and TS [also contains "Moth"] (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - "Swan Song," MS (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - "Tabula Rasa," MS reworking of published poem, author unknown (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - "Thanskgiving" ("Samhain"), pre-1990, TS (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - "That Only Song," TS [with MS of "Riddle"] (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - "There's a road between great oak trees...," ca. 1977, MS (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - "They say in my country...," MS (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - "Thrall," ca. 1974, TS (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - "Time Will Tell," 1967, TS (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - "Tiny Song," TS (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - "Tragedy," ca. 1969, TS (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - "Twice in Two Days," December 1968, TS (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - "Verses for an Anniversary," MS (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - "A Vision," April 1969 [Also published in February 1968], TS (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - "Wednesday," ca. 1973-74, MS and TS (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - "A Welcome Note," MS and TS (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - "When Rodney crashed the plane...," MS (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - "When the brother came home from Australia...," TS (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - "Where He Is," ca. November 1969, TS (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - "The Whole World" [See: "The Month of Maine"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "Winter Girl" (aka "Wintergirl"), February 1969, TS (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - "'Winter Song with Promises'," ca. 1970, TS [c.f. "Winter Song," 1970, in Winter Song Christmas, 1971] (Box 147, Folder 31)